Zaki: Welcome to Latifatul Fitri
Zaki: Thank you for being available to join the user testing session today
Zaki: Introduce my name is Zakiyah Hamidah, a computer science student from Jakarta State University
Zaki: Today, we will do a user testing session
Zaki: namely, user testing on the fruitin application which was developed by myself
Zaki: Before starting, I will explain the scenario of today's user testing session
Zaki: First of all, later I will give some basic questions to latifa as a respondent
Zaki: Then after that, I will ask Latifa to share your smartphone display screen
Zaki: and ask you to download fruitin app from play store
Zaki: Then you can run the application on your smartphone and after that I will ask for opinions, either criticism or suggestions
Zaki: and also give you a question regarding the fruitin application
Zaki: Is it clear, latifa?
Latifa: Already
Zaki: Okay, so I'll just start today's user testing with some basic questions
Zaki: First of all, could you introduce yourself first? starting with name, age
Zaki: occupation, domicile, play store email address, phone type, android version level of your cellphone?
Latifa: ok, introduce my name is Latifatul Fitri
Latifa: I am 24 years old and my current job is as a Customer Service
Latifa: My domicile is in the mill, East Jakarta
Latifa: my play store email address is tipahtipeh9@gmail.com
Latifa: My phone type is Android Samsung version Andorid 11
Zaki: Okay fine
Zaki: Next question, Do you or your family like fruit? and can you give the reason?
Latifa: I like it, because my family and I really like fruit
Latifa: Every day or every week there is fruit consumption
Latifa: because fruit is complementary and for health too
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Then, do you often eat fruit? if so, how often do you or your family eat fruit?
Latifa: Personally it's rare
Latifa: But my family eats fruit almost every week
Zaki: What fruit do you or your family eat often?
Latifa: at home it's usually papaya, avocado, watermelon
Zaki: Then, do you often remind others to consume fruits?
Latifa: Often eats fruit
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Then, do you know the nutritional value of these fruits?
Latifa: I know
Latifa: For the nutritional value of fruits, they are good for health too
Latifa: Then also as a vitamin supplement
Latifa: like vitamin C or vitamin B or something else
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Then, lastly, have you ever followed a diet program?
Zaki: If yes, what foods or fruits do you eat when you are on a diet?
Latifa: For now I never go on a diet
Zaki: Okay, fine
Zaki: Okay, since the question is done
Zaki: it's your time to share screen
Zaki: So, you can share your smartphone display screen
Zaki: You can run some features on the fruitin app
Zaki: You can also give your opinion, either criticism or suggestions on the application
Latifa: Regarding the app
Latifa: It's been good
Latifa: However, maybe you can add more to the list of fruits
Latifa: Added more
Latifa: Then I was also looking for apples in the search, it doesn't seem to show up
Latifa: And for the others it's okay
Zaki: You can open or try other application features on the fruit list
Latifa: Is this it?
Zaki: yes
Latifa: Already
Zaki: Then you can go back, and you can try to open the bookmarks menu
Zaki: Does the feature work well or not
Zaki: What do you think?
Latifa: It's been good
Latifa: Here is also every fruit, given an explanation regarding the fruit itself
Latifa: So we know better the nutritional content of these fruits
Latifa: Is it good to eat or not
Latifa: Moreover, there are those who are running a diet program
Latifa: For Information it's good enough
Latifa: Maybe the only drawback is when I want to look for fruit, nothing shows up
Zaki: Then, do you think this application needs additional features?
Latifa: An additional feature may be the previous one, namely the addition of the list of fruits to be even more
Latifa: because I personally think that's enough
Latifa: But surely according to other people want to see more
Latifa: Want to find out information related to what the content of the fruit looks like
Latifa: Then also can be favorite
Latifa: if possible there is a favorite feature, so that users can add their favorite fruit to find information related to the nutritional content of the fruit
Zaki: Alright, I'll ask you a few more questions
Zaki: In your opinion, does this application meet your expectations?
Latifa: It's appropriate
Latifa: It's been really good
Zaki: Then,....
Zaki: The search feature in your opinion should be improved
Latifa: Iya
Zaki: And also increase the fruit list
Zaki: Apart from that, are there any other criticisms or suggestions regarding this application?
Latifa: Maybe add a user profile
Zaki: For the appearance of the application itself, can you give an opinion about the design of this application display?
Latifa: In my opinion the design is good, simple, and to the point with what we want to look for
Latifa: It's obvious
Latifa: no need to bother anymore to look for it
Zaki: So, do you think that the design of this application is in line with expectations?
Latifa: Yes, it's very much in line with expectations
Latifa: Then, do you think this application is useful enough to use?
Latifa: Very useful, moreover it's good for health too
Latifa: So whatever we eat we can see the content
Latifa: if it's good for our bodies, it will definitely be very useful information from this fruitin application
Zaki: Then in your opinion, is this application suitable for someone who is on a diet program?
Latifa: It fits perfectly
Latifa: It fits very well, so we can know what fruit we will eat each day
Latifa: So let's not continue to eat the fruit
Latifa: So it's been very good and helps people who are going on a diet program
Zaki: okay that's it, you can just close the app
Latifa: Good
Zaki: First, I want to ask a few more questions regarding this fruitin application
Zaki: In your opinion, is there anything that needs to be changed or added to this application?
Latifa: Maybe, just a little extra so that the icons of the fruits are minimized
Latifa: There were 2 columns, they can be reduced so that we can know more at a glance
Zaki: Described more?
Latifa: Iya
Zaki: Oh yeah, can you please rate the app and leave a comment on this app
Zaki: Can you share the screen one more time?
Latifa: wait, share screen again?
Zaki: Yes
Zaki: Then you can rate or comment on the app in the play store
Latifa: In the play store, right?
Latifa: Would you give a star?
Zaki: Yes, it is appropriate to rate this fruitin application
Latifa: Done
Zaki: Thank you to Latifa for her assessment
Zaki: Okay, you can stop sharing screen
Latifa: Done
Zaki: Ok, Thanks to Latifatul Fitri for being available to be a respondent
Zaki: in today's user testing session
Zaki: Thank you for the time and opportunity
Zaki: More or less sorry, wassalamualikum wr.wb
Latifa: Wa'alaikumsalam wr.wb
Zaki: Thanks to Latifa