Zaki: Welcome to Wardah Nabila Rusyda
Zaki: Thank you for being available to do user testing today
Zaki: First of all, my name is Zakiyah Hamidah, a computer science student from Jakarta State University
Zaki: Thanks for the availability
Zaki: First I will explain first
Today's user testing scenario
Zaki: I will explain the fruitin application first
Zaki: Fruitin application is an application that displays the nutritional value of fruits
Zaki: This application will help users to find some nutritional content in fruits
Zaki: Then for today's user testing scenario, after the introduction, I will ask some basic questions first
Zaki: After that, I will give Wardah time to display Wardah's smartphone share screen
Zaki: and also give wardah time to install the fruitin application and run it on your smartphone
Zaki: Then after running the application you can give an opinion in the form of criticism or suggestions on the application
Zaki: and also I will ask questions regarding the fruitin application
Zaki: So let's just start today's user testing with basic questions
Zaki: First of all can you introduce yourself first?
Zaki: starting from name, age, occupation, domicile, play store email address, cellphone type, and android version level?
Wardah: Introduce my name Wardah Nabila Rusyda
Wardah: 22 years old
Wardah: as a student
Wardah: domiciled in Gresik
Wardah: The email address for the play store is wardahnr@gmail.com
Wardah: The type of cellphone is Samsung Android, Android version 11
Zaki: Then, the next question, Do you or your family like fruit?
Wardah: Honestly, for me, I only like certain fruits
Wardah: But if my family likes it, I usually eat fruit every day
Zaki: What fruit is Wardah's or family's favorite fruit?
Wardah: Personally, I like mango or papaya
Warsah: My family usually eats apples or pears
Zaki: Then, do you or your family often consume fruit?
Zaki: If yes, how often do you or your family eat fruit?
Wardah: I rarely eat fruit lately
Wardah: But if it's season, for example, every day
Wardah: Because mango is seasonal, so when it's season it can be every day
Wardah: But if it's not in season, maybe once a week
Wardah: If the family eats fruit every day
Zaki: Then, do you often remind others to eat fruit?
Wardah: No, because I rarely eat fruit myself
Zaki: Then, do you know the nutritional value of the fruits you consume?
Wardah: Depends on the fruit
Wardah: usually the famous ones, like oranges, contain vitamin C
Wardah: If the others don't know
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Then, the last question, Have you ever or are you following a diet program?
Zaki: If yes, what foods or fruits do you eat when you are on a diet?
Wardah: If you join a diet program, never
Wardah: But if you're on your own diet, you just eat less
Wardah: If you eat fruit for your diet, never and don't go on a diet with fruit
Wardah: just reduce the amount of food
Zaki: So just reduce the amount of food huh
Wardah: Yes
Zaki: Fine, since the question is finished
Zaki: Time to share screen
Zaki: so you can display the share screen of your smartphone display
Zaki: and install the fruitin application
Zaki: Can you share the screen?
Wardah: Yes, wait..
Zaki: Okay
Wardah: Have you seen it?
Zaki: Already seen
Wardah: Fruitin ya?
Zaki: Ya
Zaki: Once installed later you can run the application
Wardah: So it's up to me to explore, right?
Zaki: Yes
Zaki: You can explore the app
Zaki: Yeah Maybe there's a little problem here in the search section
Wardah: Oh okay
Zaki: What do you think about Wardah?
Zaki: What do you think about this fruitin application?
Wardah: Good
Wardah: This is to find out the nutrition of fruits, right?
Zaki: Yes
Zaki: The purpose of this application is to display the nutritional content of fruits
Zaki: what do you think about the groove on this fruitin app?
Zaki: Is the plot easy to understand or is it still complicated?
Wardah: It's not confusing because we can immediately choose the fruit we want to see the nutrition of the fruit
Wardah: The bookmarks can't appear yet, right?
Zaki: Yes, it looks like there is a problem with this bookmarks feature
Zaki: so later it will probably be an input for me to fix it
Wardah: Yes
Wardah: It can also look like this
Wardah: Great
Zaki: According to Wardah, are there any other problems with this fruitin application?
Wardah: I don't know if it's made for Indonesians or foreigners because when I was looking for mangoes, it turned out to be mango
Wardah: so I can't find it
Wardah: so let's just name it
Zaki: The problem with the language, huh?
Wardah: Yes
Wardah: this is English, I think it's Indonesian
Zaki: Then, what do you think about the appearance of this fruitin application design?
Zaki: Has it met your expectations or is it still not right?
Wardah: Maybe in my opinion the appearance is on the sugar icon and others
Wardah: colored on a white background on the icon so that it blends in with this pink background
Wardah: if you can maybe change it to an icon that doesn't have a background color
Wardah: So it looks better
Zaki: Thank you for entering wardah
Wardah: Yes
Zaki: Then, do you think this application is useful enough to use?
Wardah: Helpful
Wardah: Maybe at the beginning you can give a pop up that this application is to see the nutrition of fruits
Zaki: Information pop up
Wardah: Yes, the initial appearance is like the sentence "welcome", so it looks more friendly
Zaki: Thank you for entering
Zaki: Then, next question
Zaki: Do you think this application is suitable for someone who is on a diet program?
Wardah: For the diet program.......
Wardah: For example, if someone else's goal is to eat fruit
Wardah: Maybe we can add features for people who are on a diet, such as simple questions or quizzes
Wardah: Like the question "do you want fruit with how many calories?"
Wardah: it's like a recommendation of which fruit is better by using a simple quiz
Zaki: additional recommended features you mean ?
Wardah: Yes
Zaki: Thank you for entering it again
Zaki: After this, can you give a rating on the fruitin app on the play store?
Zaki: Give stars and also comments for feedback on this application
Wardah: Okay
Wardah: Now or later?
Zaki: Can you do it now
Wardah: same comment?
Zaki: Yes, as input for the future
Zaki: Ok, thanks to Wardah, you can stop sharing screen
Zaki: Finally, I will give a summary of today's user testing
Zaki: So in your opinion, the features that are lacking or there are problems are in the search feature and the bookmarks feature
Zaki: Then also you give suggestions to add a fruit recommendation feature for people who are on a diet program
Zaki: Then you also give suggestions on the icon in the fruit details
Zaki: Is it really wardah?
Wardah: That's right
Zaki: Okay then let's end the user testing session today
Zaki: Thanks again to Wardah Nabilah Rusyda for being available
Zaki: Thank you, more or less sorry, Wassalamualaikum wr.wb.
Wardah: Waalaikumsalam wr.wb.