Zaki: Welcome to Cindi Tri Fitikasari
Zaki: Thank you for being available to take part in user testing today, which is Saturday, December 25, 2021
Zaki: First, introduce my name, Zakiyah Hamidah, a computer science student from Jakarta State University
Zaki: First - first I will explain about this fruitin application
Zaki: this fruitin application is an application that displays the nutritional value of various fruits
Zaki: This application will help users to find some nutritional content in fruits
Zaki: Then, first of all I will explain the user testing scenario today
Zaki: Later, after the introduction and also after this explanation
Zaki: I will ask some basic questions
Zaki: Then after that, there will be time for you to share your smartphone display screen
Zaki: and run the fruitin application
Zaki: Then after that, I will ask your opinion and ask some questions about the fruitin application
Zaki: So let's start today's user testing with basic questions
Zaki: first of all, can you introduce yourself first?
Zaki: Starting from your name, age, occupation, domicile, play store email address, type of cellphone, android version of your cellphone?
Cindi: introduce my name is Cindi Tri Fitikasari
Cindi: I am currently a student at the State University of Jakarta majoring in Computer Science
Cindi: and domiciled in East Jakarta, Ciracas
Cindi: Then for the type of Android cellphone version 11
Zaki: The email address for the play store?
Cindi: Her email address is cindirifs@gmail.com
Zaki: Okay, let's move on to the next question
Zaki: Do you or your family like fruit?
Cindi: Yes, I happen to like fruit at home
Cindi: Maybe almost everyone likes fruit
Zaki: Then, what is the favorite fruit for Cindi and Cinda's family?
Cindi: maybe your favorite fruit is the one you often make at home, like oranges or melons
Cindi: And........
Cindi: Banana
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Then, how often do cindi and cindi's family eat fruit every day?
Cindi: You could say quite often or every day
Zaki: Then, does Cindi often remind others to eat fruit?
Cindi: If that's not the case, because it depends on the individual itself
CIndi: So never remind others
Zaki: Then, does Cindi know the nutritional value of the fruits she consumes?
CIndi: As for the content of the fruit, maybe I only know the basics
Cindi: Like oranges contain vitamin C
Cindi: Don't know calories etc.
Cindi: I only know the basics that are usually mentioned
Cindi: I don't know much about it
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: The last question, Has cindi ever been or is she currently following a diet program?
Zaki: If yes, what food or fruit does Cindi consume while on a diet?
Cindi: I happen to have never been on a diet
Cindi: Never participated in the program either
Zaki: Okay, fine
Zaki: Okay, since the question is done
Zaki: time to share screen
Zaki: So, I'm giving you a chance to share screen
Zaki: and install the fruitin application from the play store
ZAki: Then, run it on your smartphone
Cindi: OK, does this share screen have to be installed or when you install the application?
Zaki: from scratch install it
Cindi: Have you performed yet?
Zaki: Already
Zaki: You can explore the app
Zaki: How are the features,...
Zaki: You can share your opinion, either criticism or suggestions about the application
Cindy: Okay
Cindi: This is not all the fruit, right?
Cindi: I mean, there's something that doesn't exist like that
Zaki: Yes, the fruit list isn't complete yet
Zaki: There's only what's written on the app
Cindi: this is clicked
Zaki: Yes you can
Cindi: If you go to bookmarks, it doesn't exist, right?
Zaki: oh yeah maybe there is still a problem with the bookmarks feature
Cindy: Yes already
Cindi: I have tried
Zaki: since you've tried it, I'll ask you what you think about this fruitin app
Cindi: Maybe his opinion was that there were some fruits that weren't there yet
Cindi: but maybe later with the passage of time the list of fruits can be added
Cindi: For the appearance it's good
Cindi: simple
Cindi: immediately there is a list of pictures of the fruit and the name of the fruit
Cindi: here is the name of the family and the genus
Cindi: any info on carbohydrates and others
Cindi: Maybe for people who don't know.....
Cindi: how much does our body need for carbohydrates and protein
Cindi: Maybe the information needs to be added
Cindi: Because if it's just information like this it might be considered
Cindi: just for info
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Then, in your opinion, which features have problems or problems with the application?
Cindi: The first one has a bookmarks feature, which is adding fruit to bookmarks
Cindi: It looks like there was a crash
Zaki: Maybe you can try again, because it looks like it's loading
Zaki: So it seems a bit slow to respond
Cindy: That's right
Cindi: Can you do this search or not?
Cindy: Not yet
Zaki: Yes, it seems that there are still problems with this search feature
Zaki: Then is the flow in this application easy to understand or is it still complicated?
Cindi: For the plot, because this is just to provide information about the nutritional fruits
Cindi: Pretty easy to understand
Zaki: Ok, thanks for the suggestion
Zaki: then for the view, you think it's good enough, right?
Cindi: Yes, it's good enough to see
CIndi: The colors match too
Zaki: Then, do you think this application is useful enough to use?
Cindi: Yes
Cindi: To display information is enough
Cindi: but maybe in the future more information can be added
Zaki: That's enough
Zaki: Can you give a rating or comment on the play store for this fruitin application?
Cindi: Now or how?
Zaki: Yes now
Cindy: Already
Zaki: Ok, thanks to cindi for the rating
Cindi: Can this stop share screen?
Zaki: Oh yes you can stop sharing the screen
Zaki: Okay
Zaki: Maybe I will summarize your opinion earlier
Zaki: Maybe you said earlier that the search and bookmarks features are still having problems
Zaki: Then, you also give suggestions to add information related to nutrition for our body
Zaki: and also suggest adding to the fruit list for more
Zaki: Is it true?
CIndi: That's right
Zaki: Thank you cindi for the criticism and suggestions on the fruitin application
Cindi: Iya sama - sama zakiyah
Zaki: Because today's user testing session is over
Zaki: I once again thank cindi for her availability
Zaki: more or less sorry, wassalamualaikum wr.wb
Cindi: Waalaikumsalam wr.wb
Zaki: Thank you cindi